This Christmas season, Prudential
Vietnam collaborated with the Vietnam Children's Protection Fund to
bring joy to child patients
undergoing treatment in Ho Chi Minh City
and Hanoi through a series of meaningful activities
expressing love and care.
Hundreds of Christmas gifts were recently
given to child patients at
Children's Hospital 1 in Ho Chi Minh City.
This is the opening activity for a program to
donate 2,600 gifts worth a total of 800
million VND, implemented in
Ho Chi Minh City and Hanoi during this year's holiday season,
carried out by Prodential Vietnam in collaboration with the Vietnam Children's Protection Fund
.
The support activities carried out
recently have brought many
practical benefits to children, helping
disadvantaged children across the
country to have a better life
.  And we always hope that
CEN will continue to be an important partner,
a strategic partner, to work together with the
fund for Vietnamese children to build
practical programs and projects.
The journey of spreading love will
continue to reach more child patients, with the
next stop being
Hanoi Children's Hospital on December 22nd. This
is also part of Proential's long-term commitment
to responsible business and
sustainable development during its 26
years of partnership with Vietnam.